stockhouse.com 2018-06-25

# Stockhouse-Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy

Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

This Privacy Policy applies to Stockhouse Publishing Ltd., its subsidiaries, and any website containing the Stockhouse name (collectively "Stockhouse").

###  Condensed Version

This condensed version is a summary of and subject to the "Complete Privacy Policy" and is provided for your convenience only. We encourage you to read the "Complete Privacy Policy" below.

####  Scope

This Privacy Policy applies to personal information collected by Stockhouse and sets out how the company will safeguard your privacy.

####  Collection

  * We collect personal information directly from you and will have sought your consent to do this.
  * We collect information such as you name, contact information and/or other information when you register with us, subscribe to our newsletters, submit content to our site, participate in a contest or use our recommendation service. We collect financial information when you place an order for a product or service.
  * We do not collect personal information about you if you only browse our website. We use cookies and other facilities so that it is easier for you to use our website. These mechanisms store information about your preferences, enabling you to take full advantage of our services. For more information, see the "Complete Privacy Policy", under "How do we use IP addresses and cookies, and other tracking facilities?"

####  Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

  * We use your personal information to provide you with financial products and services and to perform our regular and necessary business functions.
  * We may disclose your personal information to organizations that carry out functions on our behalf and to other third parties where the product or service requires this disclosure.
  * We may also share your personal information within Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. and our joint venture partners to tell you about other products and services we offer.
  * If you buy something from us, we will disclose your personal information to the extent necessary to fulfill your order and if applicable, charge your credit card.
  * We do not sell your personal information to outside companies.
  * For more information see the "Complete Privacy Policy", under "How does Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. use your personal information?" and "How does Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. disclose your personal information?"

####  Accessing Your Personal Information and Opting Out of Marketing

  * In most cases, you can access the personal information we hold about you, and modify the personal information we hold about you; for more information see the "Complete Privacy Policy", under "How can you deactivate your account or correct/revise information that we have about you?"
  * You can opt out of receiving marketing material from us at any time; for more information, see the "Complete Privacy Policy".
  * You can withdraw your consent to our use of your personal information at any time, but if you do we may no longer be able to provide some or all of our products and services to you.

####  How to Contact Us:

If you have any questions about this policy or wish to make a complaint regarding the treatment of your personal information by us you can write to us using the web form located here: https://support.stockhouse.com/anonymous_requests/new

###  Complete Privacy Policy

Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

NOTICE: Please visit: http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/tech/privacy.shtm for important information about safe surfing from the U.S. Federal Trade Commission

This Privacy Policy applies to Stockhouse Publishing Ltd., its subsidiaries, and any of its websites containing the Stockhouse name.

Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. believes that you should understand why we collect, and how we use and disclose the personal information you provide and, furthermore, that you should have the right to approve the use of that information. In the handling of your information, Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. follows a policy of "informed consent."

In the course of using the varied features of this website, you may provide information (such as name, contact information, or other registration information) to Stockhouse Publishing Ltd., its service providers, or other businesses you contact. Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. and these entities may use, and you agree that Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. may use, this information as well as technical information about your use of this website, or communicate separately with you.

Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. will not provide our users' personal information to companies you have not interacted with. Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. will not disclose your personal information, except as described herein, and Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. will not disclose information to others that would connect your user name with your actual name, unless Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. is compelled to do so by legal authorities. In our sole discretion, we reserve the right to make exceptions whenever we have a good faith belief that access, use or disclosure of personal information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (c) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of, Stockhouse Publishing Ltd., its users or the public.

This Privacy Statement answers the following questions:

  * What information does Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. gather about you?
  * How does Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. use your personal information?
  * How do we use "IP addresses" and "cookies" and other tracking facilities?
  * Will Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. disclose any of your personal information?
  * What kinds of security measures do we take to protect your information from accidental loss or disclosure?
  * Will Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. use your information for direct mailings?
  * How can you deactivate your account or correct/revise information that we have about you?
  * How do we respect children's privacy?
  * How long do we retain personal information we have about you?
  * What else should you know about your privacy?
  * How to Contact Us?
  * How will you know whether Stockhouse Publishing Ltd.'s privacy policy has changed?

####  What Personal Information does Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. Gather About You?

Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. collects personal and non-personal information about our users so that we can provide a more interesting and useful service, as well as more targeted advertising. We ask for your name, e-mail address, and other personal information when you register to use certain features of our website, or when you sign up for special or personalized services, such as our discussion boards or e-mail newsletters. We also may ask for this information at other times, such as when you enter contests or other promotions sponsored by Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. and/or our partners. We sometimes conduct surveys as well, although you are not required to respond to them.

If you use our recommendation service to e-mail one of our articles to a friend, you will need to provide us with your friend's e-mail address and your e-mail address as a return address. We will automatically send this person a one-time e-mail, with the recommended article attached, as well as an invite for your friend to visit and register with our site. We will not use these e-mail addresses for any other purpose.

We collect IP addresses for site security and to help us understand how people use our sites so that we can improve our sites and our users' respective experiences. For similar quality reasons, we use cookies and other facilities when you visit our site. Notations may be madein your computer for future reference. If you revisit the site, these notations allow the website to identify you as a return guest, and offer you products tailored to your interests or tastes.

When you place an order for a product or service, we need to know the sort of information typically used for credit card transactions, such as your name (as it appears on the card), mailing and billing addresses (and shipping address, if different), telephone number, and credit card number and expiration date. Gathering this information allows us to process and fulfill your order and notify you of your order status. We encrypt all of this information using Secure Socket Layers (SSL) technology.

We may also collect your e-mail address when you submit content to our sites (for example; blogs, bullboards, or group discussion entries). Unless we get your approval, we will not display your e-mail address with your submission.

We may also use tiny electronic images (called "single-pixel GIFs" or "Web beacons"), which allow us to count users who have visited specific pages or accessed certain features. We may use single-pixel GIFs in the following ways:

  * To count and recognize users
  * To conduct research on behalf of some partners about their websites
  * For auditing purposes
  * To determine aggregate information about users, including demographic and usage information
  * To determine which e-mail messages were opened and/or acted upon when we send HTML-formatted e-mail messages (messages resembling web pages that include graphics)

Advertising networks that serve ads on our site may also use single-pixel images in their advertisements. In general, any electronic image viewed as part of a web page, including an ad banner, can act as a web beacon.

####  How Does Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. Use Your Personal Information?

Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. collects personal information to provide you with the best and most personalized experience possible. It also allows us to provide our advertisers with an efficient way to reach the right audience. By knowing a little about you, Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. can deliver more relevant content and advertisements to you.

We conduct research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior based upon the information you provide us when you register or participate in contests, or other services and promotions on our site, or based upon the information on our server log files. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. We may also notify you of products, services, or areas of our site that we think may interest you based on the information we've received. If you would prefer us not to contact you for these purposes, simply go to our opt-out page and let us know.

In addition to helping us process your order, we use the information we collect from you when you buy a product or service from us so that we can provide you with an enhanced and more personalized shopping experience. We will also send occasional discount alerts and notices about products and services that we think may interest you. If you would prefer that we not send you those notices, simply use our opt-out page to let us know.

Sometimes we ask for personal information when providing special features and services. You do not have to give us that information, but without it, you may not be able to take advantage of those products or services. For example, you will be unable to track your personal stock portfolio on our site unless you input the stocks you own or watch and you may not be able to gain access to certain areas of our site unless you register and/or subscribe.

####  How Do We Use "IP Addresses" and "Cookies" and other tracking facilities?

These mechanisms are used on our sites in the following ways:

  * To access your stored account information automatically when you log on to our site, in order to deliver better and more personalized service
  * To estimate our audience size and usage patterns. The unique cookie that is given to each browser accessing Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. is then used to determine usage patterns for targeting content and ads based upon user interests
  * We use cookies to allow you to access your account information automatically, and make changes to your personal information
  * Our search engines may use cookies to expedite your search for content or products

In the course of serving advertisements to any of our sites, our web advertisers, including but not limited to DoubleClick and 24/7, may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

Some of our advertisers use third-party networks to serve their advertisements on our sites and in our HTML-formatted newsletters. Often, these third-party advertising companies use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to measure advertisement effectiveness. These companies may also use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We do not control, nor do we have access to the advertiser's cookies or the information their cookies obtain. Use of their tracking technology is subject to their own privacy policies. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

Most internet browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can configure yours to refuse cookies or notify you when you've received one. Browsers differ; check your "help" menu to learn how to change your cookie preferences. However, if you reject cookies on our sites you will not be able to access all areas of the site and your access to certain features including our Bullboards and Web Portfolio will be limited. When you accept our cookies, we cannot use them to find out who you are, unless you tell us.

For more information about cookies, read the unofficial Cookie FAQ from: <http://www.cookiecentral.com/faq/>

####  How Does Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. Disclose Your Personal Information?

Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. will not disclose any personally identifiable information about individual users, except as described in this Privacy Policy. With the few exceptions that we explain here, we do not give, rent, lend, or sell individual information to our advertisers, although we do provide aggregate information. For example, we might tell an advertiser that there are 120,000 registered users in a given city, but we will not tell them that John Smith is one of them, nor will we give them his e-mail address. We may also use this aggregated information to help the advertisers reach the kind of audience they want. They may give us an advertisement and tell us the type of audience they want to reach (for example, males in a certain area code).

Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. (or people working on our behalf under contracts and confidentiality agreements) would then take the advertisement and display it to users who have told us they meet those criteria. We may also disclose aggregate information (for example, information showing that 35 million of our readers clicked on a particular web advertising banner last month) in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.

As for individually identifiable information, we may disclose it only under the following circumstances:

  * We may disclose information to others when we have your consent
  * If you sign up for a special offer from an advertiser, we will provide your individual contact information (for example, name, mailing address, e-mail address, and/or telephone number), so that the advertiser or its agent can fulfill the special offer. Once the advertiser receives the information, it will be subject to that firm's own privacy policies; however, if you do not want a particular advertiser to have your personal information, then you should not sign up for that advertiser's offer
  * We may disclose information to selected partners, under nondisclosure agreements, only for the purpose of marketing Stockhouse co-branded offerings (such as a "Stockhouse NewsBlast" published by another company, or a "SH@The Bell" announcement); those partners will be able to use the personal information they receive from us only for marketing the co-branded offerings, not for marketing anything else - if you would prefer not to hear such announcements, simply go to our opt-out page and let us know
  * If you buy something from us, we will disclose your personal information to the extent necessary to fulfill your order and if applicable, charge your credit card. We may use a fulfillment company to fill and ship your order (excluding products you download directly from our site) and a credit card processing company to verify your card number and process the transaction. For example, if you order a Stockhouse service with your credit card, we need to give your address to the fulfillment house and your credit card information to the processing company (to confirm payment). We may also give your information to a delivery or postal service so that your order can be delivered to you
  * If you use our recommendation service to e-mail one of our articles to a friend, Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. will automatically send this person a one-time e-mail, with the recommended article attached. The e-mail address you give us will appear on the "from" line of the e-mail, thereby disclosing this information to whoever opens and reads the e-mail. Similarly, if you send e-mail from our site, by using "reply to author" or "e-mail this post," your address may appear as the return address of that e-mail
  * We may disclose your personal information as required by applicable law, or in response to legal process, to protect the rights or property of Stockhouse Publishing Ltd., or to protect the safety of Stockhouse Publishing Ltd., our users, or others
  * We may sometimes conduct mailings to other people's lists. To make it easier for us to comply with the Federal CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 (http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/buspubs/canspam.shtm), we may share our e-mail list of people who have requested not to receive promotional communications from us with the list providers (or contractors) solely so that we can avoid sending e-mails to people who have asked not to receive them (or, conversely, so that our advertisers can avoid sending e-mail to people who have requested not to hear from them). We provide these lists only to list providers or contractors that we consider to be reputable, and only under strict nondisclosure/nonuse agreements
  * We may disclose personal information in some other limited circumstances, but we will specifically describe them to you when we collect the information, such as in the rules of a contest or a new service. For example, if we are going to give personal information to a contest's sponsor, we will disclose it when you sign up for the contest, so that you can decide if you want to enter
  * We may employ contractors or other third parties to help with our operations. We may give them access to databases of user information, so that they can perform services for us, including performing system maintenance, displaying personalized content (such as portfolios), performing list analysis or management, or sending mailings for us from our advertisers. These parties are all subject to confidentiality agreements that restrict the use and disclosure of information they obtain through their relationship with Stockhouse Publishing Ltd.
  * The ads appearing on this website are delivered to you by our advertisers. Information about your visits to Stockhouse.com and its related web sites, such as the number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you
  * We may disclose your personal information to another entity as part of a merger, a sale of assets or all or part of our business, or any other corporate change or re-organization

####  What Kind of Security Measures Do We Take to Protect Your Information From Accidental Loss or Disclosure?

Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. is committed to protecting your personal information. We store information you provide us on our secure servers. Furthermore, the information you provide when making a purchase is encrypted with SSL technology.

Personalized areas of our sites, such as My Stockhouse, are password-protected. Only you have access to these password-protected areas. Do not share your passwords with anyone. Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail. If you are using a computer to which others have access, such as one in a computer lab, Internet cafe, or public library, always remember to log out and close your browser window when leaving our site.

If you have forgotten your password you may recover it by selecting the option "Forgot Password?" on the sign in page.

####  Will Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. Use Your Information for Direct Mailings?

If you register with Stockhouse Publishing Ltd. or sign up for or buy any of our products or services, including Stockhouse, we will send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services that we believe may interest you. Our partners in co-branded products may also send you information, but only for those Stockhouse branded products.

If you do not want to receive such offers and mailings, you can let us know on our opt-out page or simply to click the "unsubscribe" link found in our e-mail messages.

Please note: If you purchase products and/or services from us, or if you register for an account with us, we may contact you to confirm your purchase, subscription, or registration, or to provide you with information about its terms or features. You may wish to keep this transactional or relationship e-mail to help you use our products and services.

####  How Can You Deactivate Your Account or Edit the Information We Have About You?

If you want to correct or change information in your My Profile, or any other information we have about you, please do so by login into your membership account and selecting your member name on the right side of the top member bar and selecting "My Profile" from the drop down list.

To cancel any of your free e-mail subscriptions, do so by login into your membership account and "My Profile" and choosing the "Subscriptions" tab.

To cancel your account, please contact us using the web form located here: <https://support.stockhouse.com/anonymous_requests/new>

####  How Do We Respect Children's Privacy?

Our sites are not directed at children under the age of 13. We operate our sites in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (<http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm>) and will not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone under 13.

####  How Long Do We Retain Personal Information We Have About You?

We will retain personal information only as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes stated above, as required for legal or business purposes or as required by law. Subsequently, we will destroy, erase, or make anonymous such information.

####  LIVE Leads™ tag from KickFire®

Our website contains a LIVE Leads™ tag from KickFire®. This tag will track activity on the stockhouse.com website. KickFire’s LIVE Leads technology is not connected to any combination of personally identifiable information (“PII”), cookie identifiers, or identification tags that when combined with other information received by the servers, may be used to create profiles of the natural persons and identify them. The IP Address Intelligence used by KickFire’s LIVE Leads TWIN Caching™ technology removes those traces of PII and focuses at the firmographic level. More information can be found at http://id.kickfire.com/privacy-policy

####    
What Else Should You Know About Your Privacy?

When you post information on discussion boards, blogs, and in your personal profile, the information, along with your screen name is visible to the public. Please remember that whenever you disclose personal information publicly such information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online where people can see it, people will know that information and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. If you do not want strangers to have your e-mail address, you should not post your e-mail address on a discussion board.

Also please be aware that when you post messages on our discussion boards, people can respond to your posts via our "reply to author" e-mail function. Of course, they still will not know your e-mail address (unless you send e-mail to them).

This Privacy Policy applies to the operations of our US and Canadian sites. Data handling practices and rules may differ from country to country.

While we do our best to protect your personal information, Stockhouse cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any password and/or account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online, especially when using a computer that other people can use also.

Many of our advertisers or partners, such as brokerages, merchants, or data providers, link from our site to areas on their own sites where they sell their own products and services. If you follow links from our site to others, you should be aware that you are doing business with those other sites, which have their own privacy and data collection practices. Stockhouse has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies. For more information regarding a site and its privacy policies, check that site.

####  How to Contact Us?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or wish to make a complaint regarding the treatment of your personal information by us you can write to us using the web form located here: <https://support.stockhouse.com/anonymous_requests/new>

####  How Will You Know Whether Stockhouse's Privacy Policy Has Changed?

We may change this Privacy Statement at any time, but we will give notice of any material change (or any notices that we are required to give you) on our websites and/or in e-mail messages.

Last Updated: May 2014
